Gift shop. Various gifts as services can be bought in the shop, e.g. dining in the dark in the restaurant,
family weekend in the SPA hotel, driving Ferrari, skiing in the forest with a trainer. Services are limited
and also available on specific days (cheap staying at the hotel available if ordered in advance).
The gift can be bought any time. It is valid X months (must be ordered within that time). 
The system must be able to manage gifts and their "implementation".

Klasės:
1.Main
2.GiftBean
3.ReadFile
4.Data modifiers
5.Date
6.Logic access modifiers
7.Interface

0. Duomenų failo sukūrimas
1. Duomenų failo nuskaitymas
2. Sugalvot galutinį dizainą (dovanų pasirinkimas)
3. Logic access modifiers
4. Users
5. Interface naudojimas